hey guys,
beauty,
it was an hour.
I apologize now because I couldn't get there.
okay,
your name is,
Was it with you?
Yes,
who is responsible for the water?
I swear,
there is.
there's me in the morning
Is there a Tiririca here alone or is there a kiosk?
has no,
there is no kiosk,
has the other
here at the same mall
has a kiosk
or maintenance,
the concept that I came here to fix your day.
let me explain.
I am Caio
from office
of the Passenger,
my god how cool!
and this little ball here of yellow chocolate,
contains 20g of happiness.
my sky god,
I wanted to know how much happiness
You need it on your day today a lot.
this is the joke i make
that I learned to undertake in this creative way.
Is it on?
what's your Instagram?
Water in the world?
I think I've seen a video of you.
Have you seen a video of my bro?
I saw that you got suspicious brother
when you arrived,
right?
so I think I already know what's wrong with it,
you see suspicious galley.
see,
everything we had in the world?
Yes,
this is right
world wanted to disappear.
I travel all over the world,
right?
I travel. lost,
lost,
was lost,
it was liberation.
there I my god from heaven,
I'm not knowing anything.
and then girl,
all right?
pleasure fall beats there
I have faith.
the pix is CPF.
thank you brother,
tamo together.
goodbye,
we're together.
bro thanks boys,
the sympathy was worth it.